Yeah, I'm pulling out all the stops.
There's a 39.95 Lover's Special...
(Howard:)...at P.F. Chang's.
Yeah, egg rolls, dumplings,
bottomless wok.
Yeah, and you get your picture taken
on the big marble horse out front.
(Sheldon:)Given that Saint Valentine...
(Sheldon:)...was a third century Roman priest
who was stoned and beheaded...
(Sheldon:)...wouldn't a more appropriate
celebration...
(Sheldon:)...be taking one's steady gal
to witness a brutal murder?
(Howard:)I understand your point,
but given the choice...
(Howard:)...Jews always go with Chinese food.
(Raj:)If anyone's interested,
I'll be spending this Valentine's Day...
(Raj:)...the same way
I spend every Valentine's.
Buying rotisserie chicken,
taking it home, standing over the sink...
(Raj:)...and eating it out of the package
with my bare hands like an animal.
Okay, so to sum up,
one giant marble horse...
...one asinine comment,
one lonely man and his chicken...
...and let's see. Who's left?
Oh, that's right, my plans.